<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on </title>
    <link>/categories/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Crpytocurrency Charts</title>
      <link>/things_that_change/cryptocurrency-charts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/things_that_change/cryptocurrency-charts/</guid>
      <description>If you aren’t keen on finance or if you are new to these kinds of charts, as I was, I’ll explain them briefly:
 Each individual bars represent a day. The low point of the bars represent the low-point for the coin that day and so forth for the high/high point. The coloring represents where the coin closed that day in respect to the prior day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using tidyverse tools with Pew Research Center survey data in R</title>
      <link>/things/tidyverse-survey-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/things/tidyverse-survey-data/</guid>
      <description>What is the “tidyverse”? R is free and open-source software that anyone can contribute to. The most common kinds of contributions are collections of R code called packages. R packages are typically hosted on The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN), but can also be found on other primarily open-source code repositories like github, gitlab, or bioconductor. The ability for anyone to be able to build an R package and contribute to R’s development is a key component of R’s utility, but with so many packages (13,581 packages on CRAN as of 12/27/18), there are often many different ways to tackle the same challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>